Now, here's the corner of Ebichu's cousin Sekimei.
In this corner, Akita Prefecture's PR ambassador Akita Bikuni Girls was appointed.
Everyone from Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku will learn about the charms of Akita and share its charms.
Ebichu members visit Akita and have various experiences related to Akita.
Last time, we reported on the public recording that took place at the Akita Bunko Archive Exhibition venue.
And this time, this member will appear. Please introduce yourself.
Yes, this is Yuno Kokubo, attendance number 14 of Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku. Thank you.
Yo!
please.
Yunopi! Thank you for coming, but first of all, Kokubo-san.
This is the 7th time since April of this year that my cousin Akitako has appeared.
7th appearance.
It's amazing, because it hasn't even been 4 years since i started our activities.
yes.
Isn't it amazing that it's appeared 7 times?
That's amazing, isn't it?
It's a quest that comes about twice a year.
There are currently 9 regular members.
Does that mean it's not spinning around that much?
It's not like I'm going around, but I feel like Yuunopi often comes by.
I've actually had you come 7 times, so far it's a bit of a memory.
It's like it's popping out
Basically, Yuno has a lot of things to do with eating.
The first one was udon, right?
Udon Inaniwa Udon
Udon or cherries
And recently, grapes
Because I've been eating all the time
Fruits are great
There are some left
Certainly impressive
Did you take a photo with the cherry?
The grapes were also delicious and I had them eat them.
It also has a bit of a fruity flavor to it.
It definitely has a strong image of fruit.
I think I'll go after the fruit monster.
I feel like I'm about to turn into a monster.
fruit monster
I also try some delicious fruits from Akita.
By the way, I'm the top of the younger sister's members.
On the other hand, who is the second one?
I wonder who is the second one
Maybe
Is it Kokotan? I would say Kokotan or Nonokamaru.
But I'm just trying to win, and I'm going to continue to win.
Let's do it appropriately. Now, let's talk about Yuno's persona. I would like to touch on that part as well.
Released on Sunday, December 15th Published in Monthly Wanko Volume 13 Yunopi
After hearing this story, I'm sure it's a monthly magazine with dogs.
Yes, I took a picture with the dog.
I'm sure it's a dog sweater today too.
Yes, I was wearing something.
Did you feel like there was a dog there when you noticed it?
Yes, it was floating when I noticed it.
Although I may not have been aiming for it.
By the way, I heard that the dog was also very cute.
The name Ki-chan
Yes, my brother put it on.
My younger brother named him Ki-chan and is now 8 years old.
Probably 8 years old
Probably 8 year old Ki-chan
He says he keeps it at home.
I keep it at home
It's a toy poodle, right?
A silver toy poodle
It's a rather rare color though.
Something
He's 8 years old.
Something like 8 years old, silver and 8 years old
It looks like her back is stretched out and sharp in that photo.
I was nervous and felt like I was going nowhere.
Normally, he would glare at me a lot.
Enira will find me
He often has a rather human-like expression on his face.
So when we were filming, he really looked like a dog.
It's a dog
It has a dog feel, doesn't it?
dog feeling
They are usually quite human-like.
Since it's my dog, this time it was a dog from a dog-like magazine.
It looks like it's a dog
I he usually feel naughty?
He usually calm, but sometimes he looks at me with really shocked eyes.
I'm calm and calm
He calmly glared at me, etc.
There are quite a few moments when I feel like I probably understand what people are saying.
It's like they're talking somehow
But in the monthly edition, it seemed like a dog.
It was a dog, right?
I can only say one, but it's like that.
I want to see this photo.This is it.
You'll want to see it.
I have the impression that Kokubo-san often uploads photos like this on SNS.
In addition to TikTok, Official X also started in May this year.
And there's also Instagram
I think she's probably in charge of Ebichu's SNS.
Ah, but i am certainly a person who is quite active on SNS.
That's right, I'm having a bit of fun watching X as well.
Yunopi no X is interesting
I guess it's a little soothing
Anma Tweet from November 24th It's not often that it gets dug up.
It's around 6pm or 6pm. I thought I was going to go to the convenience store, so I went to get my wallet, and then I just went to bed and called it this time.
Well, I don't think there's anything more embarrassing than being called a tweeter.
By the way, what time did you decide to go to the convenience store?
It's probably around 2 o'clock.
I think I'll go around 2 o'clock.
The day before was amazing
There was a live concert where all kinds of people gathered, and there were so many people that I started to get tired and feel like I was getting people sick. It's gone,
When I woke up the next day, it was around 2am, so I decided to go to the convenience store to buy some juice. I thought so, but
When I came to get my wallet, she was already asleep / That's what it means to be tired.
This isn't about being lazy. yes.
Sometimes it's an attitude
Although I sometimes pinch it
I'm a little worried about the replies.
Don't push yourself like it's okay
He worries me a lot.
There are kind people
For fans
I feel like you support me
Is SNS fatigue okay?
I think I'll just stop it all
Sometimes I feel like
I'm so tired
Instagram really
I want it to be lively.
Official Instagram
law
Really?
I think only those who want to see it should see it.
Is that so?
I also think of Twitter.
Even if it's not just random people
That's like a family
I wish I had seen it in limited edition.
But maybe someone from above told me not to do it.
Yunopi, please do something, please.
I give up
In that sense, it was snowing quite nicely today.
I guess it's in Akita prefecture.
I went to the south.
I took a lot of pictures of Yuno Pigane.
In that sense
It is for SNS
Well, I thought that part was great.
thank you
I would like to do it that way, though.
You said you were busy.
There were also many live performances
Last month on November 16th at Akita Arts Theater Milhas.
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku Akita Bunkou Final
The finale ended successfully with a smile on my face.
Kokubo has been appearing on Akita Bunko since 2021.
After finishing the finale again this time
Do you have any honest feelings or impressions that you have left in your mind?
Well, we used to meet each other pretty much every year.
I guess I don't really feel it yet.
I feel like there will be another one next year.
Well, I'm coming to Akita today too.
I don't feel like I've left Akita that much.
That means I'm sure Akita Bunko is...
It was a very important thing throughout the live performance.
I'm sure the connection with Akita will never disappear.
Well, I thought, let's keep the distance just right.
It makes me happy to hear such words.
I'm happy
People feel that Akita is a natural place.
A good sense of distance
That's good, that's good
Once you get to Tokyo, you'll want to come back again.
It's like my hometown
It feels like coming back to the countryside.
Like that
There is no other place in Tokyo that is so rich in nature. I haven't even returned to Aichi, so it's quite natural like this.
Akita is the only place where you can come into contact with people, so it's very important. It's a place
I'm happy, so if it piles up with snow, it'll be a lot of fun.
I was trotting into the snow.
I thought you might like it.
I was happy in that sense.
And on Saturday the 14th of this month
At J Com Hall Hachioji
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku Christmas School Performance 2024
Twinkle Twinkle Ebiiiiiiiiii Star
It was done
This is produced by Mayama-san.
Run through the main 21 songs non-stop
Full of rare songs
The unit corner was also great.
Why don't you look back on it again?
Really this time
From the set list to the stage
Mayama-san made all the costumes and everything.
Did you make it?
Thank you for thinking about a lot of things.
Really Mayama-san's
in this song
It was a live show where I thought of everything.
Inside Myama World
It's like around Inopyu World.
Some people also watched the broadcast.
As if it was really good.
They've been posting things and things like that.
For Kokubo-san, after joining Ebichu
It's your first time having a Christmas daigakugeikai.
The unit corner was just amazing.
I also watched the broadcast.
Together with Yuna Nakamura
trioza influenza songs
It's coming soon, hasn't it been announced?
How did you feel when it was decided that you would perform this with Nakamura-san?
At first I was wondering why, but it happened at the end of last year, around December 29th. Sometimes I got the flu
The next day, Nakamura was also sick and couldn't perform at the end of the year live.
It really makes sense that the two of them had trioza influenza.
By unexpected foreshadowing recovery
To Kashiwagi-san too
I had the pleasure of doing Triozane Infrenza, and I did the line.
What did you get back?
Well, it's getting interesting
Funny with 4 letters
I said it looked interesting.
I see. In reality, the two of you were really cute in your pajamas.
It feels like a pajama party
Also, Yunopi was trying to get piggyback the middle.
That's right, the original two people, Rina-chan give Hinata-chan, a piggyback. The choreography was for Hinata to get a piggyback.
For that part, It decided Yuno to get piggyback.
I kind of want Mayama to made Yuno got piggyback.
I want you to do it
That's right, that was really Mr. Mayama's production point.
That's why Mr. Nakamura said this.
I gave a reaction that seemed a bit impossible.
Tell me it's no longer possible for both of us.
Mr. Mayama told me that it was okay even if it was impossible, so I did it.
When I was watching it, it felt like they were actually doing something on the spot as a surprise. It was fun to be there
It's like a real complaint, it's seriously impossible.
The actors were also good.
Yasumoto's costume
Is that the arm warmer? That heart on the arm warmer when he sings that solo. Isn't that part?
I heard that it was woven by Yunopi, is this true?
It's true, I originally had a completely normal version with no heart attached. I'm sorry but
Only one person is knitting
Aya-chan and I were talking about if you don't feel a little lonely.
I said, Okay, I'll knit something nice for you.
I was thinking about knitting either a ribbon or a heart.
So I made it into a heart
Wow, Mr. Otsu was amazing, right?
When I was watching the stream, I thought it was a cute costume without knowing it.
Later, I learned about the story on Kokubo's SNS.
Wow, my manual dexterity was showing.
Both of it?
Both are that
It's different because it was prepared for me.
I knitted the heart itself.
The costumers also accepted it.
He put it on
It was natural
It was really stylish with just one point.
How long does it take to knit?
That was about 30 minutes
half an hour?
Hurry
It's surprisingly easy, isn't it? No, it's definitely difficult.
That was also a point of interest. It was a live show full of coolness, cuteness, and strength.
Ebichu is gaining momentum and will have a live performance at Saitama Super Arena on March 20th.
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku 15th anniversary University Performance 2025 love & brave is about to be held
This is because the temporary ticket acceptance period has been suddenly extended. There is no doubt that the day will be very exciting.
Please tell us your enthusiasm for the university performance.
Yes, secondary sales such as upgrade tickets have already started.
I'm doing it now.
I'm kind of wondering what will happen to the tickets though.
My goal at Ebisu Junior High is
cam
It's about making people sell out, so of course entertaining is already basic. for the next step with it as
Our goal is to sell it out, so by then we'll have another live show in the new year. I'm going to try my best to do that.
My goal, or rather my enthusiasm, is to reach that Saitama Superlina. This is amazing. I'm sure March 20th will become a legendary day.
I've reached the perfect age. It's my birthday, March 20th. Oh yeah, look, look, just when I turned 18, I was called Saitama Super Arena.
Super maybe
10 18歳になった人でこの場所
I don't think anyone stood up that day.
I would like to engrave my name on Saitama Super Arena.
It's going to be a wonderful and monumental day.
So we are really supporting them with all our might towards that end.
And this time in Yuzawa City, I had a colorful experience where my hands became even more dexterous.
So please listen
Cousin Ishi Akita
Now, Ebichu's Cousin Ishi Akita, this time we came to Yuzawa City.
yes
Yes, please, please, I'm awake. It's okay. I'm awake. It's too bright, so I don't know where to look.
I know what it feels like to close your eyes and fall asleep the next moment if it's too bright.
Yuzawa City is known for its area of ​​heavy snowfall, and you can see the surrounding mountains. It looks like it's covered in snow.
It's so bright.I understand the meaning of wearing goggles at ski resorts.
Now that you understand, I'm like, why am I doing this?
Yes, that's right, the weather is nice. Today is a good day for location shooting.
It turns out that Yunopi has also been knitting recently.
That's right, I've been really into knitting lately.
I made some earmuffs and made them for my friends, so I gave them as gifts yesterday as well.
Aren't earmuffs made by craftsmen like earmuffs?
I have received a request for something.
That's right, Yunopi was trained by knitting.
I think he's dexterous with his fingertips.
probably
In that sense, I would like Yunopi World to be fully demonstrated here.
This is what bothers you
Kawamen Lacquerware Traditional Crafts Museum
Good read
Even though I didn't wave the money
I did some research beforehand
I asked many people beforehand.
I thought it was too hard to read.
You might read it as Kawaren.
It's Kawazura lacquerware.
It's Kawamo lacquerware.
It's lacquerware that has been passed down along the river in Yuzawa City.
Although it is a pottery, it has a history that continues from the Edo period.
A history that continues from the Edo period
amazing
Yes, there is.
By carefully finishing the groundwork and making it
Being able to create something durable and unbreakable
This may be a characteristic of the Kawazuhara style.
This time
This is the technology related to the Kawazuhara style.
I would like you to experience it
From that Edo period
I want to go back to the Edo period
Return to the Edo period
Well then, let's take a moment with the samurai.
Feeling like a town girl
Let's go then
yes
oh
I entered the store here.
For large spaces, I use chopsticks and bowls.
There are many lined up
I understand that Kawazu-like clothes were often used for everyday use.
Yes, like chopsticks.
There are so many of them.
There are many different types.
Certainly
You can experience a lot of techniques, but today I'll be here to help you.
This is Hiroki Setsu from the Urushi Studio Bushi. Thank you very much, Setsu-san. Thank you very much for your support.
So, Setsu-san this time. What kind of things can national defense personnel experience?
Today we will be painting the final finishing touches on Kawazura lacquerware, called wrapping paper. From the final finishing touches
We're going to do it once we've skipped everything, so it's the last step. But it also feels like important work.
Well, the gold and other colored illustrations above are drawings.
Painting is done using lacquer, a technique that has been passed down since ancient times.
Draw a picture with a brush and add gold or silver powder on top of it.
The process involves rolling the powder.
You can tell that the colors are vivid.
There are actually a lot of colors like blue and green.
It seems that each person has a different way of applying patterns and colors.
This means that you can create original works.
This time, I used a round container with a diameter of about 10 cm as a canvas.
this is
We are trying to expand the national defense's unique world, the so-called Yunopy World.
What about unopy?
I really don't know what to draw first.
I can't draw illustrations of all sorts of traditional Japanese flowers, so I was wondering what to do. I'm here
I can't draw, so maybe I'll ask you to draw something original.
I agree
Well then, let's do our best and give it a try.
please
Now, Yunumi is wearing an apron and has a badge on her chest. .
It already has something from Akita culture.
Yes, I have something on.
There was something on it.
It's exclusive.
thank you.
please.
I learn techniques in places like this.
Mr. Seto, what kind of work do you do first?
First, start by choosing the design you want to draw.
You will also choose the color of the plate.
black and red.
There are plates for each, but which one would you like?
Then black please
Why did you choose black again?
Because I liked black better
Shidoro is in the middle of nowhere
So, Seto-san, now that you have chosen this option, how do you proceed from now on?
From now on, it will be difficult to draw where there is nothing.
We have prepared 4 types of simple sketches today.
You can choose a sketch from there.
There are four types of sketches drawn on round pieces of paper.
What are the four types this time?
This time, there will be four types of cherry blossoms: rabbit, plover, and camellia.
Everything is wonderful, but
Which of these four types will you choose for the black plate?
I'm currently torn between cherry blossoms and rabbits and don't know what to do.
Make it a rabbit.
Yes, please.
Ah, I'm going to make it a rabbit.
Now, let's draw a sketch of the rabbit.
Place this thin paper on a plate and trace it with a brush.
Then it will look like this
amazing
It's better to hit from the front to the back.
I think it would be easier to start from where you started.
Now, here's a sketch.
First, I'm going to transfer a little bit to this plate.
Let's try it by tracing.
using waveforms
Yes, can I do it?
Press it well
I'll probably fly from here.
You're doing it carefully.
Do you think it's on?
please
Should I put a little more effort into it?
I hope it's on
I hope
Oh! It's on
It went down nicely
Then I'll actually draw a picture according to this.
Setsu-san, how should we proceed from here?
From here, it's time to start painting with lacquer.
This is a pretty thin brush.
I agree. It may be a little difficult and difficult, but please try your best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
How thin will it be?
It's less than 1mm thin.
Hey.
In fact, when you were in elementary school, maybe you used a thin brush like this for any of them. ?
I think it's much thinner than the brush at that time, so I'll do my best.
So, from here on, it's a fairly delicate process that requires manual dexterity.
Let's actually dip the lacquer into the brush and trace it downwards.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Is lacquer red? Is it vermilion?
This is colored to make it easier to see.
Pinkish in color.
It's painful though. I feel like I don't know where to start. Indeed, where should I start drawing? If your hand shakes, everything will be shaken.
It might be a little more difficult to draw than with regular paint, so I like to draw from top to bottom and from top to bottom. It might be easier to draw if it looks like this.
It's at the rabbit's pampas grass. It is drawn in a slightly circular manner.
I ended up getting thinner, a mess. Isn't everything going well?
Is it thin? It's okay.
Yudopi is currently drawing pampas grass. I have now finished drawing the pampas grass on the left. From there, I entered the pampas grass on the right.
The tip is a really thin brush, but the lacquer appears to be applied well.
It's starting to be fun. I changed the angle of the plate slightly. Isn't it easy to draw? Well, you draw it well.
Well, Mr. Yuki, how do you like Yunopi's brush strokes?
Ah, it's okay. It's good for a first time. I'm good at it.
thank you.
I'm being praised.
Yay!
Ah, but I'm scared of rabbits. Drawing rabbits is important, really.
I left the rabbit here.
yes. Where do you want to start drawing?
Where does the rabbit come from?
Is it a body part?
Do you want to fill it all in?
Fill it.
That might be better.
When filling in, draw the outline with a line,
yes.
Even if you apply it thickly, it won't work, so I will apply it thickly.
You can draw the edges and then fill in the inside.
I'm drawing from the ears.
First, draw the edges of the ears.
It started from my left ear.
I naturally started filling it in.
It lightly fills the ears.
The ears fit in nicely.
Yes, this is exactly as Yukizu-sensei ordered.
I boldly used a brush to fill in the left and right ears, as well as the left and right ears.
I won't be able to say anything.
Oh, it's a radio, but that's fine. Yuzumi please concentrate. It's totally fine.
I think I should draw the moon.
I'm leaving, hot water moon.
I don't know what to do, maybe I should use the sun instead. The sun on the other hand?
That's fine.
Yes, a cute sun is drawn now.
Ah, there's nothing wrong with the shape. So finally let's draw the shrimp.
Can you draw a shrimp? It's at the bottom of the page.
Ah, tiny shrimp. It's shrimp. Yes, I think that's enough, shrimp.
This is a pretty realistic shrimp. I can draw it now.
OK.
Okay, so it's just a sketch, but I drew it and Usa-chan filled it in properly. Then, there was pampas grass around, and Kokumo Yu was in a box, and on top was a smiling sun. , small shrimp at the bottom.
yes.
Yunopy World. wonderful.
It is difficult to get into a position that makes it easy to draw while rotating the plate properly, so everyone Mr. is good at it.
thank you.
What kind of work will be done next?
From here I will add colored powder.
Choose your favorite color from 6 colors of powder and apply it.
What we actually provide is
There are 6 colors: red, blue, green, purple, gold, and silver.
Thank you for your preparation
Ask Yunobi to choose her favorite color from these
I would like to actually remove that color.
This pampas grass?
This part will be colored silver and blue.The rabbit will be colored gold.
Make the sun and shrimp green and make the name part red.
It's nice and has a unique color sense. This involves actually removing the powder.
Well, what is the process like?
Usually usually
I use cotton to apply the powder. Today we will be working on putting powder into a cylinder called a powder cylinder and dropping it in a flop.
Today, I would like Kokumo-san to finish it with her own hands.
I'll do my best, but I feel like I can make it.
But I'm worried that even an amateur can do this. What do you think?
Let's try our best
Shall we start with green?
Is it a wooden tube?
This is Yoshi
Reed? Does it look like bamboo?
I agree
Thin bamboo
I'm going to press it patter patter patter
amazing
So please try this a little bit.
From something like a thin cylindrical bamboo
Finely chop
While tapping with your fingers
But the color is coming out
But if you do it forcefully, it will come out all at once.
It's going to go to a completely different place.
It's difficult, very
I danced a little though
Well, I guess that kind of thing might happen.
We are removing the powder as we accept it.
This might be a little difficult, but
It's difficult, because it ends up scattering all over the place.
It's difficult
The sun and pampas grass are close, so I have to be careful here.
But is this colored?
It's okay, and the shrimp.
Yes, shrimp are green too.
At first, it was like tapping
Once some powder has fallen off, I'll gently stroke it.
Ah, I'm good at it
Eh, beautiful
It became beautiful
I'm going to take this extra piece of green.
Yes, now I'm dusting off the excess green on the plate.
It highlights the color of the sun on the small plate.
Oh, beautifully done
interesting
Added to favorites
Next main event
Come on, it's Usa-chan.
What color was Usa-chan?
Usa-chan is golden
I'm going with Supeta, so it's okay if I fall in the middle.
Yunopi is currently using a bamboo tube to drop gold powder.
It's difficult.
It's a little difficult. Once it's attached to a certain extent, I'll finish it off with cotton.
Then do the same thing, quietly.
Now, it's gold in color. It is entering the rabbit nicely.
The area here is large, so it's going well, albeit little by little.
The gold color went all the way to Usa-chan's feet.
Beautiful, amazing.
What do you think? This is quite beautiful.
Yes, it turned out quite nicely.
The golden color was great, Usagi.
The golden color was growing on it, giving it a very rabbit-like feel.
What kind of luxury?
I feel embarrassed to be live-lived.
It's quite embarrassing, isn't it?
Well, there is no live broadcast of the Kiei experience.
You may have never heard of it
Now you have a cloth to put your droppings in.
Finally, we will finish the rabbit.
How do you finish a rabbit?
The last one is a slightly shaved piece of this bamboo stick.
rabbit's
I will finish by carving out the face etc.
yes
Scrape, well today.
Take a look at your face
It's like drawing
yes
Eh, Yunopi shaves it?
Yeah
Huh?
Couldn't Yunopi do this?
No, you definitely can't.
Then, the face
Add only the eyes part yourself
eye area
Can you see it?
yes
Please put your eyes in
Now, let's put the eyes in.
On Yunopi's side
Whoa, quite boldly
It's difficult. Because you'll get fat.
Make it into a circle.
I saw round eyes. It feels crisp.
Maybe eyelashes?
Yes, I tried it.
cute.
It's completed.
Yes, it is now complete.
thank you.
Yes, it was done.
amazing.
Inoue, what do you think of the finished product?
But something...
Even if you have never done it before, you can still ask for help.
It turns out to be such a beautiful vessel.
You can also add your own new designs.
I think I was able to create an original feel.
It certainly feels like that. It even has a name on it.
No, it's already my first time and I've done well.
thank you
I think it's great because it has individuality and originality.
Yay!
So let's take this and go back to the studio.
yes
I heard that you said yes.
This time I came to Yuzawa City to experience Kawazu-like scroll paintings.
No, it was a delicate task for Yunopia, but I had a lot of fun doing it.
Well, surprisingly, I also like drawing illustrations.
I haven't used a brush this thin very often, but it was a lot of fun.
That's right, it was fun and you want to see Oda's work, right?
Yes I want to see it
Thank you very much for bringing it.
amazing
There's a lot of attention to detail in the details.
If you look closely at the rabbit's eyes, you'll see eyelashes growing out.
Underneath the meadow where the rabbits are running
It also includes an illustration of a shrimp.
this is
Did you do any drafts?
This shrimp and tire part is done without drafting.
What can I say?I went there based on my intuition.
You went all out, didn't you?
There is no hesitation in the brush, but it catches my eye when I look at it quickly.
It has a really eye-catching accent.
There is also a name written in katakana that says the mother of the country.
It's so cute
It's nice to see a very pop feel in traditional crafts.
Mr. Setsuhiro, the teacher at Urushi Kobo Bushi.
While raising my voice a little more like Koho,
The score is also 100 out of 100.
Because he told me
Has this helped you gain confidence in things like drawing?
But she helped me a lot with the coloring and it turned out really nice.
I'm going to decorate it once and use it from now on.
I plan on displaying it for a while and using it a lot from now on.
By the way, how do you use the specifications?
What's good?
I guess you could call it a small plate.
Now, peel the oranges and set aside the oranges.
It's nice to keep peeled oranges around.It seems like it will expand your worldview.
Let's put all kinds of fruits here as fruit monsters.
Well, when I said yes, my level was 59 in the last public recording.
Congratulations on reaching level 60 this time.
thank you
I don't think the level is too high
It's 60. Speaking of 60, it's National Defense 4. He has been active in the world of professional baseball since six years before he was born.
Saitama Seibu Lions player Takeya Nakamura, I'd like to take a second look at you. This is the uniform number of this player. Actually, it's 60.
He boasts a total of 478 home runs in professional baseball. I'm a home run artist though.
I would like to introduce one of Nakamura's famous quotes.
Is the body the most important thing?
I believe that if your body moves, your technique and mind will be stable.
Although I did a slightly strange imitation.
Did these words resonate with you?
As long as you are healthy
I thought it was okay
thank you
Health above all else
From hitting a home run that depicts a beautiful treasure ship.
Like Nakamura, who is called an artist.
Yunopi is sure to bring the whole family together
It should be possible to create a beautiful arch.
This is the word
Yunopi really said that too.
Please take care of your body
Let's rush this to SSA
And once again, I would like to ask Mr. National Defense Yuno.
What is Akita for Yuno as the mother of the country?
A place where you can interact with nature
That's right
It's not about echoing.
It was nice to be natural.
I've heard it said many times, I'm sure.
Yuno's beauty comes into contact with nature.
I'm glad I got to see your beautiful smile.
Please continue to come into contact with nature in Akita.
Lastly, please give a message from Kokumo to the listener family.
From Akita
Saitama Super Arena is a little far away.
I'm also coming to Akita, so I hope everyone will come too.
I would be happy if you could come to Saitama Super Arena.
Above, City ABC, system number 14
It was Yuno Kokubo from Akita Binokuni Girls.
Bitten
Have a great new year